今天早上我們已經有了很好的敬拜讚美禱告
我們想到當日先知以色列看見了耶穌華榮耀的意象
我們看見神的寶座
看見神的威榮
那個時候他的心裡就發出來一個響應
我在這裡請拆遷我
今天早上我們又深深地感受到神的威榮 神的偉大
我們願意像先知以色列一樣 再次把我們的生命完全奉獻給最為值得我們奉獻的主
從心底下也發出來同樣的呼聲 我在這裡請拆遷我
從心底下也想回應神 說:主,我正在這裡
耶穌登山變相的時候
耶穌在祂的嘴裡哭泣 顯出祂的神性的榮耀
在那樣的情景之下 試圖逼著說我們在這裡真好
各位弟兄姊妹 各位同工 各位同工
我們的主真好 我們的主真好 我們跟從祂是何等的榮耀
我們跟從祂是何等的榮耀
這六天早上的茶精 這是六天早上的茶精
主義目的就是跟隨基督
我們不能不跟隨基督
這位榮耀的基督在前面引導我們
我們整個的生命都被基督吸引
我們無體投地那樣在主的面前
我們嚮往祂
跟隨基督是何等的權利
是何等的榮耀
是何等的喜樂
茶精會 我們把重點放在主的話語上
我們今天早上要從菲律賓書第一章來看
跟隨基督的基礎
就是與主合一
請大家翻到菲律賓書
一件非常寶貴的書
我們想到與主合一的時候
當我們思考到與主合一的主題
一節的經句立刻浮現在我們的心中
One golden verse surface in our mind
一章二十節
21 Verse 21
21 節 Verse 21
因為我活著就是基督
For to me to make is Christ
這是基督教信仰的一個最高的表達
This is the highest manifestation of Christianity
我活著就是基督
For me to live is Christ
這句話在石頭堡羅的生命中
世風中展現
顯明出來
And this statement about the life of Paul
is fully manifested
原來這句話太抽象
太崇高
太高調
Actually this word is so abstract
It's of a high level
但是當我們看石頭堡羅的表現的時候
But then as we witness the manifestation upon Paul
立刻我們感覺這句話何等的真實
何等的寶貴
Immediately we can understand it's so precious and so real
我活著就是基督
For me to live is Christ
有三個意思包括在這句話裡頭
Three meanings are included in this statement
是如基督而活
To live like Christ
第二為基督而活
To live for Christ
第三 and the fourth
藉基督而活
To live through Christ
如基督而活是我們向基督
To live like Christ
Which we want to imitate Jesus Christ himself
他的形象從我們身上顯出來
That is his image upon us is being manifested
為基督而活是我們生活的目標
和基督一樣
To live for Christ
That is our aim coincide with the purpose of Jesus Christ
藉基督而活是讓基督的生命的能力
在我們裡面發揮出來
To live through Christ
So that the power of Jesus Christ through us is being manifested
我們沒有一個人能藉自己的力量來活著就是基督
There is no one who can live by his own self and to be like Christ
當基督在我們裡面的時候就不同了
But when Christ is in us then it is totally different
內居的基督同在的基督
把他自己藉著我們活出來
The immanent the indwelling Christ
Through our body is being manifested
我們想到如基督而活
To live like Christ
保羅在羅馬書第八章二十九節這樣說
(英文)
我要把這一節讀出來給大家聽
很熟悉的一節聖經
(英文)
八章二十九節
因為他預先所知道的人就預先定下
效法他兒子的模樣
使他的兒子在許多地球中做長子
(英文)
在這兩節裡面
二十八二十九裡面
告訴我們神兩重的雙重的預定
(英文)
首先
Verse twenty and verse end
(英文)
Who are called according to his purpose
That God in Christ has predestined us
Has saved us
(英文)
This is the predestination of salvation
And then
(英文)
Verse twenty nine
For those whom he foreknew
就預先定下效法他兒子的模樣
He also predestined to be confirmed to the image of his son
(英文)
That God in us wants us to be like Christ
The twofold predestination
(英文)
To predestine us to be saved
To be like Christ
(英文)
To be confirmed to his son
And to imitate him
(英文)
Many Christians only know about the first predestination
That I have been elected and saved
(英文)
Such a grace and such a privilege
And we do not know about the second fold of predestination
(英文)
Because of that we never press forward to be like Christ
在我們的心中有非常清楚的輪廓
How I desire that this twofold predestination will be drawn and drawn in our hearts
(英文)
So that I can live for Christ and live like Christ
And also for his sake that I live
(英文)
That the purpose of Jesus Christ is our purpose
Someone who study well
(英文)
Upon the earth Christ Jesus has no hand and he has used our hands
On the earth he has no legs he has used our legs
(英文)
And he doesn't have a mouth so he has used our mouths
Our whole being is united with the purpose of Jesus Christ
(英文)
So that we live for Christ
In this conference
(英文)
We have a very clear objective
In this great commission we are the lead for Christ
(英文)
So that the commission that Christ entrust us will not be obeyed
Such is the great and all known mission for us
(英文)
It is very much closer for the second coming of Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ second coming become the greatest motivation for the preaching
(英文)
And also when the live for Christ
Praise God
(英文)
That the power of Jesus Christ is together with each and every one of us
There is a verse from the Bible that become the source of my strength
(英文)
Second coming 10 to the 12 was mine
Christ Jesus told Paul
(英文)
That my grace is sufficient for you
Because my power is manifested upon who he who is weak
(英文)
And Paul said even more I would boast about my own weaknesses
There is no one who is willing to boast about his own weaknesses
(英文)
But he who boasts about his own weaknesses
It is because he knows that Christ Jesus power will be manifested upon those who are weak
(英文)
Once more I want to accept this Bible verse with no harm
For for me to live is Christ
(英文)
We want to see in chapter 1 how that Paul had been living
With Jesus Christ
(英文)
According to the outline that we have on hand I want to speak accordingly
The first
(英文)
Paul in chapter 1 verse he said I am united with Christ's affection
I will read for you
(英文)
I have experienced the heart of Christ
And I miss you all
(英文)
This is something that God can witness for me
To experience the heart of Christ
(英文)
I remember that in the past the Bible was translated in English as
In the bowels of Jesus Christ
(英文)
In the heart of Christ
That is the cry of Jesus Christ himself
(英文)
is now living within us
When we read the book of Philippians
(英文)
We can naturally find how many times
the word joy has been used
(英文)
We can naturally find how many times
the word joy has been used
(英文)
17 times